
{
    "quiz": [
        {
            "name" : "sports",
            "list" : [
                {
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Which one is correct team name in NBA?",
                    "options": [
                        "New York Bulls",
                        "Los Angeles Kings",
                        "Golden State Warriros",
                        "Huston Rocket"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Huston Rocket"
                },{
                    "id": 0,
                    "question": "Which Indian cricketer did the miracle by making a century in 20 balls in T-20 match? ",
                    "options": [
                        "Rishabh Pant",
                        "Shubhmaya Das",
                        "Riddhiman Saha",
                        "Hardik Pandya"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Riddhiman Saha"
                },{
                    "id": 0,
                    "question": "Which of the following Grand Slam tennis tournaments offers the highest total prize money? ?",
                    "options": [
                        "Australion Open",
                        " French Open ",
                        " Wimbledon",
                        "US Open"
                    ],
                    "answer": "US Open"
                },{
                    "id": 0,
                    "question": "Who bagged India's first medal at the 21st Commonwealth Games 2018 ?",
                    "options": [
                        "Saikhom Mirabai Chanu",
                        "Virdhawal Khade ",
                        "Srihari Nataraj",
                        "Gururaja"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Gururaja"
                },{
                    "id": 0,
                    "question": "Which one of the following teems was defeated by India to win the Women's Hockey Asia Cup title, 2017? ",
                    "options": [
                        "Japan",
                        "China",
                        "South Korea ",
                        "Pakistan"
                    ],
                    "answer": "China"
                },{
                    "id": 0,
                    "question": "Which Cup/Trophy is associated with the game of Hockey?",
                    "options": [
                        "Phyanchand Trophy",
                        "Davis Cup",
                        "Merdeka Cup ",
                        "Wimbledon Trophy"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Phyanchand Trophy"
                  }
            ]
        }, {
            "name" : "maths",
            "list" : [
                {
                    "id": 0,
                    "question": "5 + 7 = ?",
                    "options": [
                        "10",
                        "11",
                        "12",
                        "13"
                    ],
                    "answer": "12"
                },{
                    
                    "question": "(12 - 8) + 2 = ?",
                    "options": [
                        "1",
                        "2",
                        "3",
                        "6"
                    ],
                    "answer": "6"
                },{
                    
                    "question": "5 + 8 = ?",
                    "options": [
                        "1",
                        "2",
                        "3",
                        "13"
                    ],
                    "answer": "13"
                },{
                    
                    "question": "(2 * 2) + 5 = ?",
                    "options": [
                        "1",
                        "2",
                        "3",
                        "9"
                    ],
                    "answer": "9"
                },{
                    
                    "question": "(5 - 2 ) * 5 = ?",
                    "options": [
                        "1",
                        "2",
                        "15",
                        "4"
                    ],
                    "answer": "15"
                },{
                    
                    "question": "(12 + 8) / 2 = ?",
                    "options": [
                        "10",
                        "2",
                        "6",
                        "4"
                    ],
                    "answer": "10"
                }
            ]
        },{
            "name" : "dance",
            "list" : [
                {
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Which among the following is a martial dance?",
                    "options": [
                        "Kathakali",
                        "Bamboo dance in Meghalaya",
                        "Chhau of Mayurbhanj",
                        "Bhangra of Punjab"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Chhau of Mayurbhanj"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Which from the following is a Classical dance form?",
                    "options": [
                        "Bhangra",
                        "Bharatanatyam",
                        "Chhau",
                        "Wangala"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Bharatanatyam"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "With which of the following dances Raja Reddy is associated with?",
                    "options": [
                        "Bharatnatyam",
                        "Kuchipudi",
                        "Odissi",
                        "Kathakali"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Kuchipudi"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Gidda is a popular folk dance from which state of India?",
                    "options": [
                        "Punjab",
                        "Haryana",
                        "Uttar Pradesh",
                        "Uttarakhand"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Punjab"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Who had popularized the Indian classical dance abroad?",
                    "options": [
                        "Kelucharan Mohapatra",
                        "Rukmani Devi",
                        "Gopi Krishna",
                        "Uday Shankar"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Uday Shankar"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Which among the following is a folk dance of India?",
                    "options": [
                        "Manipuri",
                        "Bihu",
                        "Kathakali",
                        "Bharatanatyam"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Bihu"
                }
            ]
        },{
            "name" : "art",
            "list" : [
                {
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Madhubani a style of folk paintings, is popular in which of the following states in India?",
                    "options": [
                        "Bihar",
                        "Madhya Pradesh",
                        "West Bengal",
                        "Rajasthan"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Bihar"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Warli painting is indigenous to which State?",
                    "options": [
                        "Gujarat",
                        "Rajasthan",
                        "Odisha",
                        "Maharashtra"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Maharashtra"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Nand Lal Bose, Manjit Bawa, Tyeb Mehta are?",
                    "options": [
                        "Classical Singers",
                        "English Poets",
                        "Photographers",
                        "Painters"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Painters"
                }
            ]
        },{
            "name" : "technology",
            "list" : [
                {
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "OS computer abbreviation usually means ?",
                    "options": [
                        "Order of Significance",
                        "Open Software",
                        "Operating System",
                        "Optical Sensor"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Operating System"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": ".MOV extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
                    "options": [
                        "Image file",
                        "Animation/movie file",
                        "Audio file",
                        "MS Office document"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Animation/movie file"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Changing computer language of 1's and 0's to characters that a person can understand is?",
                    "options": [
                        "Highlight",
                        "Clip art",
                        "Decode",
                        "Execute"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Decode"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "How many bits is a byte?",
                    "options": [
                        "4",
                        "8",
                        "16",
                        "32"
                    ],
                    "answer": "8"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Blue is what number on the resistor color code?",
                    "options": [
                        "4",
                        "8",
                        "2",
                        "6"
                    ],
                    "answer": "6"
                }]
        },{
            "name" : "geography",
            "list" : [
                {
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Guwahati is situated on the banks of river?",
                    "options": [
                        "Brahmaputra",
                        "Ganga",
                        "Yammuna",
                        "Godavari"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Brahmaputra"
                }, {
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "The Gulf of Mannar is situated along the coast which state in India?",
                    "options": [
                         "Karnatka",
                         "Kerala",
                         "Andhra Pradesh",
                         "Tamil Nadu"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Tamil Nadu"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": " With reference to the climate of India, the western disturbances originate over which one of the following ?",
                    "options": [
                        "Arabian Sea",
                        "Baltic Sea",
                         "Caspian Sea",
                         "Mediterranean Sea"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Arabian Sea"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "In the Uttar Pradesh and Madhya Pradesh states, the joint Rajghat River Valley Projectis launched on",
                    "options": [
                        "Ken River",
                         "Son River",
                         "Chambal River",
                         "Betwa River"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Betwa River"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Where is Thattekad Bird Sanctuary located ?",
                    "options": [
                        "Kerala",
                        "Tamil Nadu",
                        "Karnataka",
                        "Andhra Pradesh"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Kerala"
                },{
                    "id" : 0,
                    "question": "Which one of the following areas of India does not come under the zone of high seismic intensity ?",
                    "options": [
                        "Uttarakhand",
                        "Karnataka Plateau",
                        "Kachchh",
                        "Himachal Pradesh"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Karnataka Plateau"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
